Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
"Summoned to court
to answer for the crimes
"of your bannerman Gregor Clegane.
the Mountain." Er...
"Arrive within the fortnight
or be branded an enemy of the crown."
Poor Ned Stark.
Brave man. terrible judgment.
Attacking him was stupid.
Lannisters...
don't act like fools.
Are you going to say something clever?
Go on. say something clever.
Catelyn Stark took my brother.
- Why is he still alive?
- Tyrion?
Ned Stark.
One of our men interfered.
speared him through the leg
before I could finish him.
Why is he still alive?
It wouldn't have been clean.
Clean.
You spend too much time worrying
about what other people think of you.
I could care less
what anyone thinks of me.
That's what you want
people to think of you.
It's the truth.
When you hear them whispering
"kingslayer" behind your back.
doesn't it bother you?
Of course it bothers me.
A lion doesn't concern himself
with the opinions of the sheep.
I suppose I should be grateful
that your vanity
got in the way
of your recklessness.
I'm giving you half of our forces -
30.000 men.
You will bring them to Catelyn Stark's
girlhood home
and remind her that Lannisters
pay their debts.
I didn't realize you placed such
a high value on my brother's life.
He's a Lannister.
He might be the lowest of the Lannisters.
but he's one of us.
And every day that he remains a prisoner.
the less our name commands respect.
So the lion does concern himself
with the opinions of...
No. that's not an opinion. It's a fact.
we are no longer a house to be feared.
Your mother's dead.
Before long I'll be dead.
And you...
and your brother
and your sister
and all of her children.
All of us dead.
all of us rotting in the ground.
It's the family name that lives on.
It's all that lives on.
Not your personal glory.
not your honor.
but family.
Do you understand'?
Hmm.
You're blessed with abilities
that few men possess.
You're blessed to belong to the most
powerful family in the Kingdoms.
And you're still blessed with youth.
And what have you done
with these blessings. huh?
You've served as a glorified
bodyguard for two kings -
one a madman.
the other a drunk.
The future of our family will be determined
in these next few months.
We could establish a dynasty
that will last a thousand years.
Or we could collapse into nothing.
as the Targaryens did.
I need you to become the man
you were always meant to be.
Not next year. Not tomorrow.
Now.
You're in pain.
I've had worse. my lady.
Perhaps it's time to go home.
The South doesn't seem
to agree with you.
I know the truth Jon Arryn died for.
Do you. Lord Stark'?
Is that why you called me here.
to pose me riddles?
Has he done this before?
Jaime would have killed him.
My brother is worth a thousand of your friend.
Your brother...
or your lover?
The Targaryens wed brothers
and sisters for 300 years
to keep bloodlines pure.
Jaime and I are more
than brother and sister.
We shared a womb.
We came into this world together.
We belong together.
My son saw you with him.
Do you love your children?
- With all my heart.
- No more than I love mine.
- And they're all Jaime's.
-  Thank the gods.
In the rare event that Robert leaves his whores
for long enough to stumble drunk into my bed.
I finish him off in other ways.
- In the morning. he doesn't remember.
- You've always hated him.
Hated him? I worshipped him.
Every girl in the Seven Kingdoms dreamed
of him. but he was mine by oath.
And when I finally saw him
on our wedding day in the Sept of Baelor.
lean and fierce and black-bearded.
it was the happiest moment of my life.
That night he crawled on top of me.
stinking of wine.
and did what he did.
what little he could do.
and whispered in my ear. "Lyanna."
Your sister was a corpse
and I was a living girl
and he loved her more than me.
When the king returns from his hunt.
I'll tell him the truth.
You must be gone by then -
you and your children.
I will not have
their blood on my hands.
Go as far away as you can.
with as many men as you can.
Because wherever you go.
Robert's wrath will follow you.
And what of my wrath. Lord Stark?
You should have taken the realm for yourself.
Jaime told me about the day
King's Landing fell.
He was sitting in the Iron Throne
and you made him give it up.
All you needed to do
was climb the steps yourself.
Such a sad mistake.
I've made many mistakes in my life...
but that wasn't one of them.
Oh. but it was.
When you play the game of thrones.
you win...
or you die.
There is no middle ground.
Come here.
Oh. yes! Oh. yes!
Oh!
Oh. yes! Oh! Oh!
Ch. yes. yes. yes. Oh!
Oh. yes! Oh. yes!
Oh!
No. no. no. no!
Is that what they teach you
up in the North?
And you -
wherever you're from -
do you have any idea
how ridiculous you sound?
Either of you understand
a thing that I'm saying?
Yes. my lord.
Let's start over. shall we?
You be the man...
and you be the woman.
Well. go ahead.
Slowly.
You're not fooling them.
They just paid you.
They know what you are.
They know it's all just an act.
Your job is to make them
forget what they know.
Now. that takes time.
You need to...
ease into it.
Go ahead.
Ease into it.
He's winning you over
in spite of yourself.
You're starting to like this.
He wants to believe you.
He's enjoyed his cock since he was old
enough to play with it. Why shouldn't you?
He knows he's better
than other men.
He's always known it deep down inside.
Now he has proof.
He's so good.
he's reaching something deep inside of you
that no one even knew was there.
overcoming your very nature.
Why don't you join us. my lord?
I'm saving myself for another.
What she doesn't know won't hurt her.
A stupid saying.
What we don't know is usually
what gets us killed.
She must be very beautiful.
No. not really.
lmpeccable bloodlines though.
I do believe my lord's in love.
For many years.
Most of my life. really.
Play with her arse.
And she loved me too.
I was her little confidant. her plaything.
She could tell me anything.
anything at all.
She told me about all the horses
that she liked.
the castle that she wanted to live in
and the man that she wanted to marry -
a Northerner...
with a jaw like an anvil.
So I challenged him to a duel.
I mean. why not?
I'd read all the stories.
The little hero always beats
the big villain in all the stories.
In the end.
she wouldn't even let him kill me.
"He's just a boy." she said.
"Please don't hurt him."
So he gave me a nice little scar
to remember him by. and off they went.
Is she still married to him?
Oh. no. He got himself killed
before the wedding...
..and she ended up with his brother.
an even more impressive specimen.
She loves him. I'm afraid.
And why wouldn't she?
I mean. who could compare to him'?
He's just so...
..good
Do you know what I learned.
losing that duel?
I learned that I'll never win. not that way.
That's their game.
their rules.
I'm not going to fight them.
I'm going to fuck them.
That's what I know.
That's what I am.
And only by admitting what we are
can we get what we want.
And what do you want?
Oh. everything. my dear.
Everything there is.
Now wash yourselves.
Both of you are working tonight.
Hmm.
You're a very lucky girl.
Do you know that?
Where I come from.
we don't show mercy to criminals.
if someone like you attacked a little lord...
at low tide we'd lay you
on your back on the beach.
your hands and feet
chained to four stakes.
The sea would come in
closer and closer.
You'd see death creeping towards you
a few inches at a time.
Where is it you come from?
The Iron Islands.
They far away?
You've never heard of the Iron Islands?
Trust me. you've never heard
where I'm from neither.
"Trust me. my lord."
You're not living in the wilderness any more.
In civilized lands.
you refer to your betters
by their proper titles.
- And what's that?
- Lord.
Why?
What do you mean. why?
My father is Balon Greyjoy.
Lord of the Iron Islands.
What's that got to do with you?
If your father's lord.
how can you be lord too?
- I will be lord after my father.
- So you're not lord now'?
No. you...
Are you having a go at me?
Is that it?
I just don't understand
how you southerners do things.
- I'm not a southerner.
- You're from south of the Wall.
That makes you a southerner to me.
You're an impudent little Wench. aren't you?
Couldn't say. my lord.
Don't know what "impunent" means.
Impudent.
It means rude. disrespectful.
Do you want to lose that chain?
Theon Greyjoy!
The lady is our guest.
I thought she was our prisoner.
Are the two mutually exclusive
in your experience?
Chances are I won't be nearby
the next time that happens.
I'm used to worse than him.
Hmm?
I'm used to men who could
chew that boy up
and pick their teeth with his bones.
Why did you come here?
Didn't mean to come here.
Meant to get much further south than this.
As far south as south goes.
before the long night comes.
Why? What are you afraid of?
There's things that sleep in the day
and hunt at night.
- Owls and shadowcats...
- I'm not talking about owls and shadowcats.
The things you speak of-
they've been gone
for thousands of years.
They wasn't gone. old man.
They was sleeping.
And they ain't sleeping no more.
I miss girls.
Not even talking to them.
I never talked to them.
Just looking at them.
hearing them giggle.
Don't you miss girls?
Riders.
The horn.
We have to blow the horn.
Why is he alone?
One blast for a ranger returning.
two for wildlings.
- three for...
- There's no rider.
Whoa. boy. whoa.
That's my Uncle Benjen's horse.
Where's my uncle?
Ned!
It's Robert.
We were hunting...
a boar...
I should have
spent more time with you.
shown you how to be a man.
I was never meant to be a father.
Go on.
You don't want to see this.
My fault.
Too much wine.
missed my thrust.
It stinks.
It stinks like death.
Don't think I can't smell it.
I paid the bastard back. Ned.
I drove my knife
right through his brain.
You ask 'em if I didn't. Ask 'em!
I want the funeral feast to be
the biggest the Kingdoms ever saw.
And I want everyone
to taste the boar that got me.
Now leave us. the lot of you.
I need to talk to Ned.
- Robert. my sweet...
- Out. all of you!
You damned fool.
Paper and ink on the table.
Write down what I say.
"In the name of Robert
of the House Baratheon.
"first Of..."
You know how it goes.
Fill in the damn titles.
"I hereby command
"Eddard of House Stark..."
titles. titles...
"to serve as Lord Regent
and Protector of the Realm
"upon my death.
"to rule in my stead
"until my son Joffrey comes of age."
Give it over.
Give it to the council...
after I'm dead.
At least they'll say I did this right.
this one thing.
You'll rule now.
You'll hate it worse than I did...
but you'll do it well.
The girl...
Daenerys.
You were right.
Varys. Littlefinger.
my brother... worthless.
No one to tell me "no" but you.
Only you.
Let her live.
Stop it. if it's not too late.
I will.
And my son...
help him. Ned.
Make him better than me.
I'll...
I'll do everything I can
to honor your memory.
My memory.
King Robert Baratheon.
murdered by a pig.
Give me something for the pain
and let me die.
Give him milk of the poppy.
He was reeling from the wine.
He commanded us to...
step aside. but...
I failed him
No man could have
protected him from himself.
I wonder. Ser Barristan.
who gave the king this wine?
His squire.
from the king's own skin.
His squire? The Lannister boy?
Such a dutiful boy
to make sure His Grace
did not lack refreshment.
I do hope the poor lad
does not blame himself.
His Grace has had a change of heart
concerning Daenerys Targaryen.
Whatever arrangements you made...
unmake them. At once.
I'm afraid those birds have flown.
The girl is likely dead already.
The stallion who mounts
the world has no need for iron chairs.
According to the prophecy...
...the stallion will ride
to the ends of the earth.
The earth ends at the black salt sea.
No horse can cross the poison water.
The earth does not end at the sea...
...there are many dirts beyond the sea.
The dirt where I was born.
Not dirts. Lands.
Lands. yes...
There are thousands of ships
in the free cities.
Wooden horses that fly across the sea...
Let's speak no more of wooden horses
and iron chairs.
It's not a chair. It's a...
..throne.
Throne.
A chair for a King to sit upon.
or...
...a Queen.
A King does not need a chair to sit upon.
He only needs a horse.
Can't you help me
make him understand'?
The Dothraki do things in their own time.
for their own reasons.
Have patience. Khaleesi.
We will go home. I promise you.
My brother was a fool. I know.
but he was the rightful heir
to the Seven Kingdoms.
Have I said something funny. ser?
Forgive me. Khaleesi.
but your ancestor Aegon the Conqueror
didn't seize six of the Kingdoms
because they were his right.
He had no right to them.
He seized them because he could.
And because he had dragons.
Ah. well. having a few dragons
makes things easier.
- You don't believe it.
- Have you ever seen a dragon. Khaleesi?
I believe what my eyes
and ears report.
As for the rest...
it was 300 years ago.
Who knows what really happened?
Now if you'll pardon me.
I'll seek out the merchant captain.
see if he has any letters for me.
- I'll come with you.
- No. no. don't trouble yourself.
Enjoy the market.
I'll rejoin you soon enough.
Psst! Jorah the Andal.
The Spider sends his greetings
and his congratulations.
A royal pardon.
You can go home now.
Sweet reds...
I have sweet reds from Lys.
Volantis and the Arbor!
Tyroshi pear brandy! Andalish sours!
I have them! I have them!
A taste for the Khaleesi?
I have a sweet red from Dorne. my lady.
One taste and you'll
name your first child after me.
My son already has
his name. but I'll try your summervvine.
Just a taste.
My lady. you are from Westeros.
You have the honor of addressing Daenerys
of the House Targaryen.
Khaleesi of the Riding Men
and Princess of the Seven Kingdoms.
- Princess.
- Rise.
I'd still like to taste that wine.
That? Dornish swill.
Not worthy of a princess.
I have a dry red from the Arbor -
nectar of the gods.
Let me give you a cask
A... A gift.
You honor me. ser.
The honor...
the honor is all mine.
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah.
You know. there are many in your homeland
that pray for your return. Princess.
I hope to repay
your kindness someday.
Rakharo.
Put down that cask.
- Is something wrong'?
- I have a thirst.
Open it.
The wine is for the khaleesi.
It's not for the likes of you.
Open it.
Pour
It would be a crime
to drink a wine this rich
- without at least giving it time to breathe.
- Do as he says.
As the princess commands.
Sweet. isn't it?
Can you smell the fruit. ser?
Taste it. my lord.
Tell me that that is not the finest wine
that has ever touched your tongue.
You first.
Me?
I'm afraid I am not worthy of the vintage.
Besides. it is a poor wine merchant
who would drink up his own wares.
You will drink.
Stop him!
Come.
You came to us as outlaws...
..poachers. rapers.
killers. thieves.
You came alone. in chains.
without friends
or honon
You came to us rich
and you came to us poor.
Some of you bear the names
of proud Houses.
others only bastard names
or no names at all.
It does not matter.
All that is in the past.
Here...
on the Wall...
we are all one House.
- Tonight...
- You're allowed to look happy.
You're going to be a ranger.
Isn't that what you always wanted?
I want to find my uncle.
I know he's alive out there.
I know he is.
I wish I could help you.
but I'm no ranger.
It's the steward's life for me.
There's honor in being a steward.
Not much. really.
But there's food.
Here...you begin anew.
A man of the Night's Watch...
lives his life for the realm.
Not for a king...
or a lord. or the honor of this House
or that House.
not for gold or glory.
or a woman's love.
but for the realm
and all the people in it.
You've all learned
the words of the vow.
Think carefully before you say them.
The penalty for desertion...
is death.
You can take your vows here...
tonight...
at sunset.
Do any of you still keep the old gods?
I do. my lord.
You'll want to take your vow
before a heart tree as your uncle did.
Yes. my lord.
You'll find a weirvvood
a mile north of the Wall.
And your old gods too. maybe.
My lord. might I go as well?
Does House Tarly keep the old gods?
No. my lord.
I was named in the light of the Seven.
as my father was
and his father before him.
Why would you forsake the gods
of your father and your House?
The Night's Watch is my House now.
The Seven have never answered my prayers.
Perhaps the old gods will.
As you wish. lad.
You've all been assigned an order.
according to our needs
and your strengths.
Halder to the builders.
Pyp to the stewards.
Toad to the builders.
Grenn to the rangers.
Samwell to the stewards.
Matthar to the rangers.
Dareon to the stewards.
Balian to the rangers.
Rast to the rangers.
Jon to the stewards.
Rancer to the builder.
Echiel to the builders.
Gordo to the stewards.
Niko to the rangers.
Escan to the rangers.
Vorkoy to the builders.
Joby to the stables.
Mink to the kitchens.
Allo to the builders.
Nelugo to the rangers.
May all the gods preserve you
Rangers with me.
Builders!
Samwell. you will assist me
in the rookery and library.
Pyp. you will report
to Bowen Marsh in the kitchens.
Luke. report to One-Eyed Joe
in the stables.
Dareon. we are sending you
to Eastwatch.
Present yourself to Borcas
when you arrive.
Make no comment about his nose.
Jon Snow.
Lord Commander Mormont
has requested you
for his personal steward.
Will I serve the Lord Commander's meals
and fetch hot water for his bath'?
Certainly. And keep a fire burning
in his chambers.
change his sheets
and blankets daily
and do everything else
the Lord Commander requires of you.
Do you take me for a servant'?
We took you for a man
of the Night's Watch.
But perhaps we were wrong in that.
- May I go?
- As you wish.
Jon. wait! Don't you see
what they're doing'?
I see Ser Alliser's revenge. that's all.
He wanted it and he got it.
Stewards are nothing but maids!
I'm a better swordsman
and rider than any of you!
- It's not fair.
- Fair?
I was singing for a high lord
at Acorn Hall
when he put his hand on my leg
and he wanted to see my cock.
I pushed him away and he said he'd have
my hands cut off for stealing their silver.
So now I'm here -
at the end of the world
with no one to sing for
but old men and little shits like you.
I'll never see my family again.
I'll never be inside a woman again.
So don't tell me about fair.
I thought you were caught stealing
a wheel of cheese for your starving sister.
Think I was gonna tell a bunch of strangers
that a high lord tried to grab my cock?
Could you sing me a song. Pyp?
I'd like to hear a song.
Now listen to me.
The old man is the Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
You'll be with him day and night.
Yes. you'll clean his clothes.
But you'll also take his letters.
attend him at meetings.
squire for him in battle.
You'll know everything.
be part of everything.
And he asked for you himself.
He wants to groom you for command.
I just...
I always wanted to be a ranger.
I always wanted to be a wizard.
-- What?
No. I'm serious.
So you'll stay
and say your words with me?
Lord Stark...a moment.
Alone. if you will.
He named you Protector of the Realm.
He did.
She won't care.
Give me an hour and I can put
a hundred swords at your command.
And what should I do
with a hundred swords?
Strike! Tonight. while the castle sleeps.
We must get Joffrey away from his mother
and into our custody.
Protector of the Realm or no.
he who holds the king holds the kingdom.
Every moment you delay gives Cersei
another moment to prepare.
By the time Robert dies.
it will be too late for the both of us.
What about Stannis?
Saving the Seven Kingdoms from Cersei
and delivering them to Stannis?
You have odd notions
about protecting the realm.
Stannis is your older brother.
This isn't about the bloody
line of succession.
That didn't matter when you rebelled
against the Mad King. It shouldn't matter now.
What's best for the Kingdoms?
What's best for the people we rule?
We all know what Stannis is.
He inspires no love or loyalty.
He's not a king.
I am.
Stannis is a commander.
He's led men into war twice.
He destroyed the Greyjoy fleet.
Yes. he's a good soldier.
Everyone knows that. So was Robert.
Tell me something.
Do you still believe good soldiers
make good kings?
I will not dishonor Robert's last hours
by shedding blood in his halls...
and dragging frightened children
from their beds.
You will sail to Dragonstone tonight.
You will place this in the hand
of Stannis Baratheon.
Not his steward...
not his captain of the guard...
and not his wife.
Only Stannis himself.
Yes. my lord.
Now leave us.
My Lord Protector.
The king has no trueborn sons.
Joffrey and Tom men
are Jaime Lannister's bastards.
- So when the king dies...
- The throne passes to his brother...
Lord Stannis.
So it would seem.
- Unless...
- There is no "unless".
He is the rightful heir.
Nothing can change that.
And he cannot take the throne
without your help.
You would be wise to deny it to him
and to make sure Joffrey succeeds.
Do you have a shred of honor?
You are now Hand of the King
and Protector of the Realm.
All of the power is yours.
You need only...
reach out and take it.
Make peace with the Lannisters.
Release the Imp.
Wed your daughter to Joffrey.
We've plenty of time to get rid of Stannis.
and if Joffrey seems likely to cause problems
when he comes into his throne.
we simply reveal his little secret
- and seat Lord Renly there instead.
- We?
You'll need someone to share these burdens.
I assure you.
My price would be modest.
What you suggest is treason.
Only if we lose.
Make peace with the Lannisters.
you say...
with the people who tried to murder my boy.
We only make peace
with our enemies. my lord.
That's why it's called "making peace".
No. I won't do it.
So it will be Stannis and war?
There is no other choice.
He is the heir.
So why did you call me here?
Not for my wisdom. clearly.
You promised Catelyn
you would help me.
The queen has a dozen knights
and a hundred men-at-arms -
enough to overwhelm what remains
of my household guard.
I need the gold cloaks.
The City Watch is 2.000 strong...
and sworn to defend the king's peace.
Look at you.
You know what you want me to do.
you know it has to be done.
but it's not honorable. so...
the words stick in your throat.
When the queen proclaims one king
and the Hand proclaims another.
whose peace do the gold cloaks protect?
Who do they follow?
The man who pays them.
Hear my words
and bear witness to my vow.
Night gathers
and now my watch begins.
It shall not end until my death.
I shall take no wife.
hold no lands.
father no children.
I shall wear no crowns
and win no glory.
I shall live and die at my post.
I am the sword in the darkness.
I am the watcher on the walls.
I am the shield that guards
the realms of men.
I pledge my life and honor
to the Night's Watch.
for this night
and all the nights to come.
You knelt as boys.
Rise now as men of the Night's Watch.
Well done. Well done.
What's he got there?
To me. Ghost.
Bring it here.
Gods be good!
What will they do to him?
When the khalasar rides.
he'll be leashed to a saddle
and forced to run behind the horses
for as long as he can.
And when he falls?
I saw a man last nine miles once.
King Robert still wants me dead.
This poisoner was the first.
He won't be the last.
I thought he'd leave me alone
now that my brother is gone.
He will never leave you alone.
If you ride to darkest Asshai.
his assassins will follow you.
If you sailed all the way
to the Basilisk Isles.
his spies would tell him.
He will never abandon the hunt.
You're a Targaryen -
the last Targaryen.
Your son will have Targaryen blood
with 40.000 riders behind him.
He will not have my son.
He will not have you either. Khaleesi.
Moon of my life.
Are you hurt?
Jorah the Andal.
I heard what you did.
Choose any horse you wish. it is yours.
I make this gift to you.
And to my son.
the stallion who will mount the world.
I will also pledge a gift.
I will give him the iron chair...
...that his mother's father sat upon.
I will give him Seven Kingdoms.
I. Drogo. will do this.
I will take my Khalasar west
to where the world ends...
...and ride wooden horses
across the black saltwater...
...as no Khal has done before.
I will kill the men in iron suits...
...and tear down their stone houses.
I will rape their women...
...take their children as slaves...
...and bring their broken gods
back to Vaes Dothrak.
This. I vow...
...l. Drogo. son of Bharbo.
I swear before the Mother of Mountains...
...as the stars look down in witness.
As the stars look down in witness.
Lord Stark!
- Stop!
-  No. all right.
It's all right.
Let him through.
Lord Stark. King Jeffrey and the Queen Regent
request your presence in the Throne Room.
King Joffrey?
King Robert is gone.
The gods give him rest.
All is accomplished.
The City Watch is yours.
Good.
Is Lord Renly joining us?
I fear Lord Renly has left the city.
He rode through the Old Gate
an hour before dawn
with Ser Loras Tyrell
and some 50 retainers.
Last seen galloping south
in some haste.
We stand behind you. Lord Stark.
All hail His Grace.
Joffrey of Houses Baratheon
and Lannister.
the First of His Name.
King of the Andals and the First Men.
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
I command the council to make all necessary
arrangements for my coronation.
I wish to be crowned within the fortnight.
Today I shall accept oaths of fealty
from my loyal councilors.
Ser Barristan...
I believe no man here
could ever question your honor.
King Robert's seal - unbroken.
"Lord Eddard Stark is herein named...
"Protector of the Realm...
"to rule as regent...
"until the heir come of age."
May I see that letter. Ser Barristan?
Protector of the Realm.
Is this meant to be your shield. Lord Stark?
A piece of paper?
- Those were the king's words.
- We have a new king now.
Lord Eddard. when we last spoke
you offered me some counsel.
Allow me to return the courtesy.
Bend the knee. my lord.
Bend the knee
and swear loyalty to my son...
and we shall allow you
to live out your days
in the gray waste you call home.
Your son has no claim to the throne.
Liar!
You condemn yourself
with your own mouth. Lord Stark.
Ser Barristan. seize this traitor.
Ser Barristan is a good man.
a loyal man. Do him no harm.
You think he stands alone?
Kill him! Kill all of them!
I command it!
Commander!
Take the queen and her children into custody.
Escort them back to the royal apartments
and keep them there. under guard.
Men of the Watch!
I want no bloodshed.
Tell your men to lay down their swords.
No one needs to die.
Now!
I did warn you not to trust me.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today